asoftmurmur.com 2019-12-18

# Privacy Policy

Sleepy Rabbit LLC ("we/us/our") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our end user licence agreement and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

### Information we may collect from you

We may collect and process the following data about you:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site [http://asoftmurmur.com](http://asoftmurmur.com/) (our site) or downloading our app (App). We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site or App.
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  * Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.

### IP addresses

We may collect information about your computer or mobile device, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

### Cookies 

Our site uses certain cookies. A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we put on your computer if you agree. These cookies allow us to distinguish you from other users of our website, which helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site. The cookies we use include "analytical" cookies. They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around the site when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily. You can change your website browser settings to reject cookies although this may impair the functionality of our website.

### Where we store your personal data

All information you provide to us is stored on secure third party servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, or to use our App, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site or through our App; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

### Merchant of record for purchases

Our upgrade order process is conducted by our online reseller Paddle.com. Paddle.com is the Merchant of Record for all our orders. Paddle provides all customer service inquiries and handles returns.

### Uses made of the information

We use information held about you in the following ways:

  * To ensure that content from our site or App is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer or mobile device (as applicable). 
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes. 
  * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
  * To notify you about changes to our site or App.
  * To process your payment card details in order to complete any payment that you make in relation to the App.
  * To create anonymised data (which we may licence to third parties directly).

If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail) with information about services similar to those which were the subject of a previous transaction with you. 

Where we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this.

### Disclosure of your information

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
  * If Sleepy Rabbit LLC or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Sleepy Rabbit LLC, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### Your rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing at any time by contacting us at [gabriel@asoftmurmur.com](mailto:gabriel@asoftmurmur.com).

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

### Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. If you do not agree with any changes you should immediately stop using your account. Continued use of your account will be deemed to be acceptance of our changes.

### Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [gabriel@asoftmurmur.com](mailto:gabriel@asoftmurmur.com).
